Hello friends, welcome to the channel. Today we will look at the
stock of ICC
Lombard General Insurance, which you
can buy by passing on your generation and
this stock is currently available at a 30% discount,
format speak and it can potentially
generate 40% of return. In this video, we will do a
very simple technical
analysis of the stock and we will also
look at
its quarterly numbers, quarterly loss,
account statement, share holding pattern,
all this, we will understand in detail the
technical analysis. If you
notice one thing here, right now the company is tweeting its 50 and
200 day movie average kilo,
number one second point, if you
look here, we draw support and
resistance lines here, so if you
notice here, at 1100, this is a
very good support for the company,
hence it shows a lot of resistance. For going above, the
second resistance
is formed, 18% is clear, if you
enter here and exit here, then
your return is formed.  27% Look, here is
a matter of swing trading. In fact, if
you look at this company in the last two years, then
it was also formed at the level of 1650.
If we look at the level of 1650 here, then
this stock is
available at a discount of 32%. Simple
theory says that if the company's
fundamentals are good quarter on quarter and
if its earnings are good, then the
stock price of the company
follows the earnings. That is,
in simple language, it means that the earnings of the company are
directly proportional
to the market price. This means that if the company is
sound, then definitely this stock will
touch the level of 1650 from here to there. When will it touch it, it will
touch it in 16 years. This means that the growth you get here is
40% on
this level. That is why in the next step we will
see what is the fundamental of the company, how is this company, how does it do
business, how does it
collect revenue, what kind of committee is there and
how much is the committee.  Now, what is the future of
this company? First of all, we have to
open the screen and see the fundamental PI of the company and the
PI of the last five years. So, there are
two very interesting things here.
First of all, the company is just trading at its medium as of today.
Its PI as of today is 305 and the
medium of the last five years has been 46.4.
This is the number one date minus you see this company's
internal value. Secondly, the
important thing to see here is that PI is decreasing
but their IPS is not consistent with
that date minus you. The
company has been rated right now. Here, the
company's
revenue from December 2019 to December
[Music]
is above Rs 17000 crore in city rate.
Operating profit is growing, in fact,
their net profit is also growing.
If we look at their metrics here,
that too over 10 years five year time
period, then they have done very well.
They have a growth of 16% in the last 10 years.  There will be sales growth and this has been
replicated in profits as well.
This has not been reflected in the average stocks and
you should notice this thing that if the company is profitable then
definitely if the company's profit increases then
definitely it impacts the share price as well.
Now if you look at their share holding pattern
here, there are mutual funds
here, they have
accumulated a lot in the last few quarters, debt money from
mutual funds and here
on this particular sector and in this
particular company we have understood that there is
no fundamental problem in this company,
why should we invest in this company, first of all
its reason
is
different insurance, although their majority
of debt comes from motor insurance
and the rest of the insurance
brings in a good amount of money directly and every insurance is
also very profitable, if you will notice one thing here,
in 2019 17% crop
insurance is the mix of their product, this is the
over period off readings which have
reduced.  The management had given guidance on
this particular cropping insurance.
However, the profit margins, or should I
say their profit margins, were
low here. Over a period of years,
they have deliberately reduced their market share here,
and elsewhere
they have held their ground. If you
look at this, the biggest thing in fire insurance and health
insurance is that the third region
over their
profit and level is
financially they are very sound companies. If you are
valuing any insurance company,
you should keep in mind that the
combine ratio tells you that if the combined
ratio is 100 kg, in terms of percentage,
if it is above 100%, then the
company is getting more premium as an
earning and their expenses are less. If the same
thing is above 100%, which means
that the company is investing more money in claims rather than
their premium. The most
important thing here is that the ICC's
combined ratio is 100% close to which this is.
Note: I would say good, but all this
is relative. How other companies in this space
compete is very
important. If you
talk about public sector companies here, their average
combined ratio is 110.
If you look at
insurance companies here, their average combined ratio is 110.
This is the combination. Second
date is only 10. Think about it. As of today, their ratio is
2.9, which is very. If you
look here, as of today, the stock currently
generates a
level of 1340.
From here, it is
1600, which gives you a return of close to
40% on investment. The ratio should be between two to
three years. So, please, if you
invest in equities here, always think
long term. If you think that
in six months, in three months, in one year,
my money will double 10 times, then you will
only be disappointed.
If your intention is
long term [Music], then definitely
this company can give you a good return. So, here is
a simple ratio of ICC Lombard General Insurance Company.  Understand or detail
fundamentalist technical analysis if you
like my video then please
like this video and subscribe channel I am
Ashish shining of thank you so much